Oh!
哦！
Hey!
嘿！
What are you doing?
你在幹什麼？
Well, you know, I was thinking of moving
嗯，你知道，我正在考慮搬家
the couch over here.
沙發在這裡。
Why would you want to do that?
為什麼要這麼做？
So that there would be a decent place
這樣才會有一個像樣的地方
for me to sit.
讓我坐下。
Great.
偉大的。
There is a decent place.
有一個像樣的地方。
And your lap does not count.
而且你的圈數不算數。
Hey, come on, help me move this.
嘿，來吧，幫我搬一下這個。
No, no, no.
不，不，不。
No?
不？
No.
不。
Rosita does not move.
羅西塔沒有動。
I'm sorry.
對不起。
Rosita?
羅西塔？
As in...
正如在...
As in Rosita does not move.
就像羅西塔不動一樣。
Joey, it's just a chair.
喬伊，這只是一張椅子。
What's the big deal?
有什麼大不了的？
The big deal is that it is the
重要的是它是
exact equal distance from the bathroom to the
從浴室到浴室的距離完全相等
kitchen and it's at the perfect angle so
廚房，它的角度非常完美
you don't get any glare coming off of
你不會感到任何眩光
Stevie.
史蒂維.
Stevie the TV?
史蒂夫電視？
Is there a problem?
有問題嗎？
No.
不。
Oh, what does he know?
噢，他知道什麼？
Come on, Rosita.
來吧，羅西塔。
Us Chico's got to stick together.
我們奇科必須團結一致。
Ow!
噢！
You bitch.
你這個混蛋。
Hey, you know what's weird?
嘿，你知道有什麼奇怪的嗎？
After you guys get married, when you introduce
你們結婚後，介紹的時候
me to people, you're going to have to
我對人們來說，你必須這樣做
say, this is my brother-in-law, Ross.
說，這是我姐夫羅斯。
Not my friend, Ross.
不是我的朋友，羅斯。
Brother-in-law, Ross.
妹夫，羅斯。
That's weird, isn't it?
這很奇怪，不是嗎？
Couldn't I just say, this is Ross?
我不能直接說，這是羅斯嗎？
Sure, do whatever you want.
當然可以，做你想做的事。
Hey, Ross.
嘿，羅斯。
So, I was checking out the real estate
所以，我正在檢視房地產
section.
部分。
Yeah?
是的？
Look at this.
看看這個。
Oh, it looks like Mom and Dad's house.
哦，看起來像爸爸媽媽的房子。
Oh, it even has a tree with a
哦，它甚至還有一棵樹，上面有
broken limb out front.
前面的肢體斷了。
And the window in the attic.
還有閣樓上的窗戶。
Oh, my God!
我的天啊！
What?
什麼？
What happened to the window in the attic?
閣樓上的窗戶怎麼了？
I can't believe Mom and Dad are selling
我不敢相信爸爸媽媽在賣
the house.
房子。
I can't believe they didn't even tell us.
我不敢相信他們甚至沒有告訴我們。
I can't believe I still don't know what
我不敢相信我還是不知道什麼
happened to the window in the attic.
發生在閣樓的窗戶。
Hello, Dad.
你好，爸爸。
Monica and I just saw the house in
莫妮卡和我剛剛看到了房子
the paper.
紙。
Guess we're surprised.
猜猜我們很驚訝。
Who did you leave a message with?
你給誰留言了？
Sorry!
對不起！
Joey, Joey, I'm so sorry.
喬伊，喬伊，我很抱歉。
I told you not to move it.
我告訴過你不要動它。
Mitch, how would you feel if, say, I
米奇，如果我說，你會有什麼感覺
wanted to move your mom, okay?
想搬走你媽媽，可以嗎？
And you said don't, and I did it
你說不要，我卻做到了
anyway, and her pad fell off.
無論如何，她的墊子掉了下來。
Okay, come on.
好吧，來吧。
Joey, I'll buy you a new one, all
喬伊，我買一件新的
right?
正確的？
We'll go down to the store right now,
我們現在就去商店
and we'll get you a new chair.
我們會買一張新椅子給你。
She's not even called yet.
她還沒打電話。
Don't you think Rosita would have wanted you
你不認為羅西塔會想要你嗎
to move on?
繼續前進？
I mean, you know, she did always put
我的意思是，你知道，她總是把
your comfort first.
您的舒適第一。
That's true.
這是真的。
Okay, you ready?
好吧，你準備好了嗎？
Yeah.
是的。
I don't want Stevie to see her like
我不想讓史蒂維看到她這樣
this.
這。
I can't believe we have to say goodbye
我不敢相信我們必須說再見
to the house we grew up in.
到我們長大的房子。
Man, some stranger's gonna be living in my
夥計，有些陌生人會住在我的
room.
房間。
Well, after 15 years of Mom and Dad
嗯，在爸爸媽媽生活了 15 年後
keeping it as a shrine to you, it's
把它當作你的聖地，它是
time the velvet ropes came down.
是時候天鵝絨繩子下來了。
I kept your room for a while.
我把你的房間保留了一段時間。
Oh, please, Dad turned my room into a
哦，拜託，爸爸把我的房間變成了
gym 20 minutes after I moved out.
我搬出去20分鐘後去健身房。
I gotta say, a tanning bed and a
我得說，一張曬黑床和一張
stack of Victoria's Secret catalogs, not a gym.
一堆維多利亞的秘密目錄，而不是健身房。
Come on, you know they love you.
來吧，你知道他們愛你。
As much as they love you?
他們有多愛你？
I was their firstborn.
我是他們的長子。
They thought she was barren.
他們認為她不能生育。
It's not my fault.
這不是我的錯。
Hey.
嘿。
I hate this year.
我討厭今年。
What's wrong with this year?
今年到底出了什麼問題？
Well, okay, it's already February, and I've only
好吧，已經二月了，我才
given two massages, and they were both the
進行了兩次按摩，而且都是
worst tippers in the world.
世界上最糟糕的小費者。
That was me and Ross.
那是我和羅斯。
Oh, that's right.
哦，是這樣。
Hey, you know, if you want to pick
嘿，你知道，如果你想選擇的話
up some extra cash, some friends of mine
一些額外的現金，我的一些朋友
made good money in college doing telemarketing.
大學時做電話行銷賺了很多錢。
Oh, that's a great idea.
哦，這是個好主意。
You're really good on the phone.
你在電話方面真的很擅長。
Yeah, and, yeah, it would probably be better
是的，而且，是的，這可能會更好
than the last telephone job I had.
比我上一份電話工作更重要。
You know, I probably won't have to say
你知道，我可能不必說
spank as much.
打屁股一樣多。
What?
什麼？
Oh, yeah, like you never called.
哦，是的，就像你從來沒有打電話過一樣。
So, basically, this is very easy.
所以，基本上，這很容易。
You read from the script, and you try
你讀劇本，然後嘗試
to sell as much toner as you possibly
盡可能多銷售碳粉
can.
能。
Okay, I can do that.
好的，我能做到。
Oh, by the way, I love my office.
哦，順便說一句，我喜歡我的辦公室。
Why don't we do a trial run?
我們為什麼不進行試執行呢？
Oh, okay.
哦好的。
Um, all right.
嗯，好吧。
Hi, this is Phoebe from Empire Office Supplies.
大家好，我是帝國辦公用品公司的菲比。
Can I speak to your supply manager, please?
我可以和你們的供應經理通話嗎？
I'm the supply manager.
我是供應經理。
Um, okay, I'd like to talk to you
嗯，好的，我想跟你談談
about your toner needs.
關於您的碳粉需求。
We don't need any toner.
我們不需要任何碳粉。
Oh, okay, well, I'm sorry to bother you.
噢，好吧，抱歉打擾你了。
Bye-bye.
再見。
Yeah, you're right, this is easy.
是的，你是對的，這很容易。
Okay, what was wrong with that call?
好吧，那通電話有什麼問題嗎？
Oh, well, all right.
哦，好吧，好吧。
Um, no offense, but you were kind of
嗯，無意冒犯，但你有點
rude.
粗魯的。
They're always going to tell you they don't
他們總是會告訴你他們不會
need toner, but that's okay.
需要爽膚水，但沒關係。
Because whatever they say, you can find the
因為無論他們說什麼，你都可以找到
answer to it here in the script.
在指令碼中回答它。
Oh.
哦。
So, I think you're ready to sell toner.
所以，我認為你已經準備好出售碳粉了。
Do you have any last questions?
最後您還有什麼問題嗎？
No.
不。
Oh, wait, yes, I do.
哦，等等，是的，我願意。
I do have one question.
我確實有一個問題。
What is toner?
什麼是碳粉？
Oh, wait.
哦，等等。
Joe.
喬.
Full bag.
滿袋。
Beer's still cold.
啤酒還是涼的。
Something terrible must have happened here.
這裡肯定發生了一些可怕的事情。
No, no, no, no, no, no.
不，不，不，不，不，不。
Stevie, I was never here.
史蒂維，我從來沒有來過這裡。
Dad?
爸爸？
I'm here.
我在這兒。
Hey.
嘿。
God, it seems like just yesterday you guys
天哪，你們這些人好像就在昨天
used to come out to watch me work.
以前常出來看我工作。
Dad, we can't believe you're selling the house.
爸爸，我們不敢相信你要賣房子。
Well, it's time for a new family to
好吧，是時候組成一個新家庭了
start their memories here.
他們的回憶就從這裡開始。
And hopefully, they're check'll clear before they find
希望他們能在發現之前檢查清楚
the crack in the foundation and the asbestos
地基和石棉的裂縫
in the ceiling.
在天花板上。
Let's just grab our stuff and get the
讓我們拿起我們的東西並得到
hell out of here.
滾出這裡吧。
I'm sorry we can't store your childhood things
很抱歉我們無法存放您童年的東西
anymore.
不再了。
Oh, it's okay.
哦，沒關係。
I can't wait to see everything again.
我迫不及待地想再次看到一切。
All the memories.
所有的回憶。
Well, I don't know what's in the boxes
嗯，我不知道盒子裡裝的是什麼
down here, but I do know that there
在這裡，但我確實知道那裡
are six or seven easy-bake ovens in
有六、七個易烘烤爐
the attic.
閣樓。
I used to love to play restaurant.
我以前很喜歡玩餐廳。
Eh, not as much as you love to
呃，沒有你喜歡的那麼多
play uncooked batter eater.
玩未煮熟的麵糊吃者。
It is unreasonable to expect a child to
期望孩子做到這一點是不合理的
wait for a light bulb to cook brownies.
等待燈泡亮起來煮布朗尼蛋糕。
So, I think your boxes are over here.
所以，我想你的盒子在這裡。
Oh, great.
哦，太好了。
Hey.
嘿。
Dad, whose cigarettes are these?
爸爸，這是誰的煙？
I don't know.
我不知道。
They must be your mother's.
它們一定是你母親的。
But please, please don't ask her.
但拜託，請不要問她。
I'll throw these away.
我會把這些丟掉。
Cool, Dad!
酷，爸爸！
My report cards.
我的成績單。
Hey, check this out.
嘿，看看這個。
Dad, math, A.
爸爸，數學，A.
Science, A.
科學，A.
History, A.
歷史，A.
Gym.
健身房。
Ooh, my rock polisher.
哦，我的岩石拋光機。
Oh, look, look.
哦，看，看。
There's your old makeup kit.
這是你的舊化妝包。
It's a clown kit.
這是一個小丑套裝。
Clown kit.
小丑套件。
Well, the white seems to be untouched.
嗯，白色的好像沒動過。
Uh-oh.
呃哦。
What?
什麼？
Do you know how the garage door opens?
你知道車庫門是怎麼開啟的嗎？
The garage floods every spring.
每年春天車庫都會淹水。
How are you ever going to sell this
你打算怎麼賣這個
place?
地方？
I think I accidentally used Monica's boxes to
我想我不小心用了莫妮卡的盒子
keep the water away from the Porsche.
讓水遠離保時捷。
Oh, no.
哦，不。
Dad.
爸爸。
What the?
什麼？
Oh, God.
哦，上帝。
Everything's ruined.
一切都毀了。
Dad, she's going to be crushed.
爸爸，她會被壓垮的。
You don't secretly smoke, do you?
你不會偷偷抽煙吧？
No.
不。
So it's just your mother, then.
那麼這只是你的母親。
This is Phoebe from Empire Office Supplies.
我是帝國辦公用品公司的菲比。
Can I speak to your supply manager, please?
我可以和你們的供應經理通話嗎？
Earl, thanks.
厄爾，謝謝。
Hi, Earl.
嗨，厄爾。
This is Phoebe from Empire Office Supplies.
我是帝國辦公用品公司的菲比。
I'd like to talk to you about your
我想和你談談你的
toner needs.
碳粉需求。
I don't need any toner.
我不需要任何爽膚水。
I'm hearing what you're saying, but at our
我聽到你在說什麼，但在我們的
prices, everyone needs toner.
價格，每個人都需要爽膚水。
Not me.
不是我。
May I ask why?
請問為什麼？
You want to know why?
你想知道為什麼嗎？
I surely do.
我當然知道。
Okay.
好的。
I don't need any toner because I'm going
我不需要任何爽膚水，因為我要去
to kill myself.
自殺。
Um, is that because you're out of toner?
嗯，是因為你的碳粉用完了嗎？
Okay, so no toner today.
好吧，今天沒有爽膚水。
Thanks anyway.
不管怎樣，謝謝。
Bye-bye.
再見。
No, no.
不，不。
Wait, wait.
等等，等等。
I can't just let you hang up.
我不能讓你結束通話電話。
Please talk to me.
請跟我談談。
Well, I only had one thing to do
好吧，我只有一件事要做
today.
今天。
I guess I could push it back.
我想我可以把它推回來。
Yeah.
是的。
Now, why do you want to kill yourself?
現在，你為什麼想自殺？
It's just that I've been working for ten
只是我已經工作了十多年了
years now at this meaningless, dead-end job,
多年來從事這項毫無意義、沒有出路的工作，
and nobody here even knows that I exist.
這裡甚至沒有人知道我的存在。
Chandler?
錢德勒？
I'm sorry?
對不起？
Look, I'm sure that people know you exist.
聽著，我確信人們知道你的存在。
Oh, yeah?
哦，是嗎？
I work in a cubicle surrounded by people.
我在一個被人包圍的小隔間裡工作。
I've been talking to you for five minutes
我已經跟你聊了五分鐘了
now about killing myself, and no one's even
現在關於自殺，甚至沒有人
looked up from their desk.
從他們的辦公桌上抬起頭來。
Hang on.
不掛。
Hey, everybody.
嘿，大家。
I'm going to kill myself.
我要自殺了。
I'll get back to you.
我會回覆你。
I got nothing.
我什麼也沒得到。
Wait.
等待。
Hey, Marge.
嘿，瑪姬。
Nothing.
沒有什麼。
A chair.
一張椅子。
Now, if anybody asks, your name is Rosita.
現在，如果有人問起，你的名字是羅西塔。
Come on, Joey.
來吧，喬伊。
I just bought you a new chair.
我剛剛給你買了一張新椅子。
The most expensive one in the store.
店裡最貴的一款。
Hey, you know what I was thinking?
嘿，你知道我在想什麼嗎？
We could name her Francette.
我們可以幫她取名為法蘭西特。
Francette?
弗朗西特？
What is she, a couch?
她是什麼，沙發？
Poor thing.
可憐的東西。
Cut down on her pride.
減少她的驕傲。
Joey, the new chair will be here in
喬伊，新主席將在
an hour.
一個小時。
Maybe we should actually move Rosita out of
也許我們真的應該把羅西塔搬出
here, you know?
在這裡，你知道嗎？
Start the healing process.
開始治療過程。
Yeah, I guess you're right.
是的，我想你是對的。
Maybe I'll take her down to the incinerator.
也許我會帶她去焚化爐。
It's going to be so sad.
會很難過的。
And kind of cool.
有點酷。
Oh.
哦。
She's healed.
她痊癒了。
That's weird.
這很奇怪。
No, it's not weird.
不，這並不奇怪。
It's a miracle.
這是一個奇蹟。
It's not a miracle, Joey.
這不是奇蹟，喬伊。
I'm sure there's some explanation.
我確信有一些解釋。
Oh, there is.
哦，有。
If you want something enough and your heart
如果你想要足夠的東西和你的心
is pure wonders, things can happen.
純粹是奇蹟，事情可能會發生。
Joey, I really don't...
喬伊，我真的不...
Can you tell me how this happened?
你能告訴我這是怎麼發生的嗎？
Well, no.
嗯，不。
Miracle.
奇蹟。
No, you know what?
不，你知道嗎？
Maybe somebody came in here and fixed it.
也許有人來到這裡並修復了它。
Or something.
或者什麼。
Someone like an angel?
像天使一樣的人？
That's right, Joey.
沒錯，喬伊。
The chair angel came in and healed your
椅子天使進來治癒了你
chair.
椅子。
Get your non-believer ass out of my
把你這個不信教的人滾出我的世界
chair.
椅子。
Yeah.
是的。
Well, she'll understand, right?
嗯，她會明白的，對嗎？
It's not like I did it on purpose.
這不像是我故意的。
Dad, that won't matter to her.
爸爸，這對她來說並不重要。
Look, all my stuff is safe and dry.
看，我所有的東西都安全乾燥。
And all her stuff is growing new stuff.
她所有的東西都在增長新的東西。
See, this is exactly the kind of thing
看，這正是這樣的事情
that makes her think you guys love me
這讓她覺得你們愛我
more than you love her.
勝過你愛她。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Does she really think that?
她真的這麼認為嗎？
Well, can you blame her?
好吧，你能怪她嗎？
I don't know.
我不知道。
I suppose we may have favored you unconsciously.
我想我們可能在不知不覺中偏向了你。
You were a medical marvel.
你是一個醫學奇蹟。
The doctor said your mother could...
醫生說你媽媽可以...
Dad, Dad.
爸爸，爸爸。
I don't want to hear about it.
我不想聽這個。
Really?
真的嗎？
Well, not right now.
嗯，不是現在。
Okay, look.
好吧，看一下。
Monica came here for some memories.
莫妮卡來這裡是為了一些回憶。
Damn it, we're going to give her some.
該死的，我們要給她一些。
Okay, grab...
好吧，抓緊...
Grab some empty boxes, okay?
拿一些空盒子，好嗎？
We'll take stuff from mine and whatever we
我們會從我的東西中拿走任何東西
can pass off as hers, we'll put them
可以冒充她的，我們會把它們放在
in there.
在那裡。
Right.
正確的。
Like, uh...
就像，呃...
Here, like this.
在這裡，像這樣。
She could have made this, right?
她本來可以做到這一點，對嗎？
And this?
還有這個？
She could have won this?
她本來可以贏嗎？
This could have been hers.
這本來可以是她的。
Sure.
當然。
Oh, here.
哦，在這裡。
What about this?
這又如何呢？
Your makeup kit?
你的化妝包？
I'd feel better.
我會感覺好一些。
I am so psyched I kept this chair
我太興奮了，我保留了這張椅子
for myself.
為了我自己。
Yeah, me too.
是的，我也是。
Hey, how's the, uh, how's the miracle chair?
嘿，呃，奇蹟椅怎麼樣？
Fine.
美好的。
I know.
我知道。
Wow, you know that this thing has speakers
哇，你知道這東西有揚聲器
in the headrest?
在頭枕頭裡？
No, really?
不，真的嗎？
Yeah.
是的。
You can hook it up to your TV
您可以將其連線到電視上
and you get radio.
然後你就可以收聽廣播了。
My chair heals itself.
我的椅子會自動癒合。
Earl, you're not hearing me.
厄爾，你沒在聽我說話。
All I'm saying is that you're not alone,
我只想說你並不孤單
alright?
好吧？
Everybody hates the people they work with.
每個人都討厭和他們一起工作的人。
Hey, guy.
嘿，夥計。
Wait, what was that?
等等，那是什麼？
That sounded like someone being nice to you.
聽起來好像有人對你很好。
No, that's just the, hey, guy, guy.
不，那隻是那個，嘿，傢伙，傢伙。
He says that to everybody.
他對每個人都這麼說。
He's the worst.
他是最糟糕的。
I'd like to take him with me.
我想帶他一起去。
Alright, so, Earl, let's just forget about the
好吧，厄爾，我們就忘掉這個吧
people at the office, okay?
辦公室裡的人，好嗎？
There's gotta be someone else in your life
你的生命中一定還有另一個人
that's worth sticking around for.
這是值得堅持的。
What about, what about your family or friends
那你的家人或朋友呢
or maybe a girlfriend?
或者也許是女朋友？
Yeah, right.
是的，對。
Oh, sorry, boyfriend.
哦，對不起，男朋友。
Oh, God.
哦，上帝。
No, whatever, anything.
不，無論如何，任何事。
Hey, guy.
嘿，夥計。
Yeah, he's gotta go.
是的，他得走了。
Okay, I should, I should probably be getting
好吧，我應該，我可能應該得到
back to my thing now.
現在回到我的事情上來。
See ya.
再見。
No, I'm not finished yet.
不，我還沒說完。
Don't, don't you dare hang up on me.
不，你不敢結束通話我的電話。
The new girl's good.
新來的妹子不錯啊
Hey, guys.
嘿，夥計們。
Hey.
嘿。
I just whipped us up some easy baked
我剛剛做了一些簡單的烤的
treats.
款待。
They should be ready in about three days.
他們應該在大約三天內準備好。
That's a good one.
這是一件好事。
You hear that, Ross?
你聽到了嗎，羅斯？
Three days.
三天。
Yeah, yeah.
是啊是啊。
Oh, this will make a great memory.
哦，這將成為一個美好的回憶。
So, which boxes are mine?
那麼，哪些盒子是我的呢？
Oh, these.
哦，這些。
These are yours right here.
這些都是你的。
Okay.
好的。
Oh, a coloring book.
哦，一本著色書。
Yeah, yeah.
是啊是啊。
Oh, you love that thing.
哦，你喜歡那個東西。
You always had it with you.
你一直帶著它。
You never went anywhere without, without that coloring
沒有這種色彩，你就去不了任何地方
book.
書。
Really?
真的嗎？
Wow.
哇。
Looks like I had some trouble staying inside
看來我待在裡面遇到了一些麻煩
the lines.
線條。
Nuh-uh.
呃呃。
An old glove?
舊手套？
Oh, yeah.
哦，是的。
You love that glove.
你喜歡那隻手套。
You took it every place you went.
你去的每一個地方都帶著它。
But you never went any place without the
但你從來沒有去過任何地方沒有
glove.
手套。
Wow, look at this.
哇，看看這個。
I can't believe I even fit into this
我不敢相信我竟然適合這個
shirt.
襯衫。
Oh, this is yours.
哦，這是你的。
I don't know how that got in there.
我不知道那是怎麼進去的。
This isn't mine.
這不是我的。
Hey, this isn't my stuff.
嘿，這不是我的東西。
Ross.
羅斯.
These are your boxes.
這些是你的盒子。
Where are my boxes?
我的盒子在哪裡？
Uh, your boxes are, um...
呃，你的盒子是，嗯...
What?
什麼？
Dad?
爸爸？
Well, the garage flooded, sweetie, and it ruined
好吧，車庫被淹沒了，親愛的，它被毀了
everything in your boxes.
你盒子裡的所有東西。
I'm sorry.
對不起。
Just mine?
只有我的嗎？
I'm afraid so.
恐怕是這樣。
So, why, why wasn't Ross's stuff ruined?
那麼，為什麼、為什麼羅斯的東西沒有被毀掉呢？
And if you say the words medical marvel,
如果你說醫學奇蹟這個詞
I'm going to easy bake your head.
我要輕鬆地烤掉你的頭。
I'm sorry.
對不起。
I used your boxes to divert water away
我用你的盒子把水引走
from the Porsche.
來自保時捷。
So, wait, Ross's stuff is fine, but I
所以，等等，羅斯的東西很好，但我
have no memories because you wanted to keep
沒有記憶，因為你想保留
the bottom two edges of your car away
車的底部兩個邊緣遠離
from water?
來自水？
Well, there was also leaves and gook and
嗯，還有樹葉和古克，還有
stuff.
東西。
I can't believe this.
我簡直不敢相信這一點。
Screw it.
擰緊它。
I'm having one.
我正在吃一個。
Hey, Chandler.
嘿，錢德勒。
Hey.
嘿。
How would you like to sit in a
您想坐在
chair that fully reclines, has a rolling massage,
完全傾斜的椅子，具有滾動按摩功能，
and speakers in the headrest?
和頭枕上的揚聲器？
Yeah, I'd love to, but I've tried that
是的，我很願意，但我已經嘗試過了
so many times, they won't even let me
很多次，他們甚至不讓我
in the store anymore.
不再在商店裡了。
Well, what if I told you that you
好吧，如果我告訴你你
could do it in my apartment?
可以在我的公寓裡做嗎？
Are you telling me that you bought the
你是告訴我你買了
chair that is making all other lounge systems
製造所有其他休息室系統的椅子
obsolete the chair that SIT Magazine called Chair
廢棄 SIT 雜誌稱為 Chair 的椅子
of the Year?
年度最佳？
I just purchased the Lazy Boy E-Kleiner
我剛買了 Lazy Boy E-Kleiner
3000.
3000。
Well, that's awesome.
嗯，那太棒了。
That's great.
那太棒了。
What made you do it?
是什麼讓你這麼做的？
Well, it's a long story, but I broke
好吧，這是一個很長的故事，但我崩潰了
Joey's chair.
喬伊的椅子。
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
哇，哇，哇。
You broke Joey's chair?
你弄壞了喬伊的椅子？
Yeah.
是的。
I thought I broke Joey's chair.
我以為我弄壞了喬伊的椅子。
That's why I replaced it with mine.
這就是為什麼我用我的替換它。
Oh, that's how it got fixed.
哦，原來如此，就這麼解決了。
What did you think?
你覺得怎麼樣？
That elves came in and fixed it?
那個精靈進來修好了？
No.
不。
Angels.
天使們。
I'm getting my chair back.
我要拿回我的椅子。
What?
什麼？
Wait.
等待。
Well, looks like it wasn't healed after all.
嗯，看來還是沒有痊癒。
So, I guess this chair is mine now.
所以，我想這張椅子現在是我的了。
Joey, you broke my chair.
喬伊，你弄壞了我的椅子。
Your chair?
你的椅子？
Yeah, he thought he broke your chair, so
是的，他以為他弄壞了你的椅子，所以
he switched the chairs.
他換了椅子。
So, there was no miracle?
那麼，奇蹟就沒有發生嗎？
No, Joe, no miracle.
不，喬，沒有奇蹟。
Oh, no, this is devastating.
哦，不，這是毀滅性的。
My faith is shaken.
我的信念動搖了。
I'm so glad I have the new chair
我很高興擁有新椅子
to get me through this difficult time in
讓我度過這段困難時期
my life.
我的生活。
Uh-uh.
呃呃。
Nice try, but you don't get that chair
不錯的嘗試，但你沒有得到那把椅子
anymore, all right?
再這樣，好嗎？
That is my chair now.
現在那是我的椅子。
You can sit on my lap.
你可以坐在我腿上。
No, I take that back.
不，我收回那句話。
I think I should get the chair.
我想我應該得到椅子。
Wait.
等待。
How do you figure it?
你怎麼想的？
Because you broke a chair, and you broke
因為你打破了一張椅子，你也打破了
a chair.
一張椅子。
The only one here that hasn't broken a
這裡唯一一個沒有壞掉的
chair is me.
椅子是我。
No, no, no.
不，不，不。
This chair's not going anywhere.
這張椅子哪裡也去不了。
Well, where's the logic in that?
那麼，這其中的邏輯在哪裡呢？
The logic is that there are two of
邏輯是有兩個
us, and we are both strong enough to
我們，我們都夠強大
break a chair in half.
將一張椅子折成兩半。
So, Joey breaks my chair, and I get
所以，喬伊打破了我的椅子，我得到了
nothing.
沒有什麼。
That's right.
這是正確的。
What are you guys, like a gang or
你們是什麼人，像幫派還是
something?
某物？
Yeah, we are.
是的，我們是。
We're the Cobras.
我們是眼鏡蛇。
Excuse me.
打擾一下。
Could you tell me where I could find
你能告訴我在哪裡可以找到嗎
Earl?
伯爵？
He's the supply manager here.
他是這裡的供應經理。
Sorry, I don't know any Earl.
抱歉，我不認識伯爵。
I'm right here!
我就在這裡！
Hello.
你好。
I'm Phoebe.
我是菲比。
Phoebe?
菲比？
The lady who sells toner?
那個賣爽膚水的女士？
Um, look, you can't kill yourself.
嗯，聽著，你不能自殺。
Look, um, I really appreciate you coming down.
聽著，嗯，我真的很感謝你能下來。
No, no, I can't, I can't let you
不，不，我不能，我不能讓你
do it.
做吧。
Why?
為什麼？
Because it was fate that made me call
因為命運讓我打電話
you today.
今天的你。
I thought it was toner.
我以為是碳粉。
No, think about it, okay?
不，你想一下，好嗎？
This isn't even my regular job, okay?
這甚至不是我的日常工作，好嗎？
And my first day on the job, you're
我上班的第一天，你
my first call.
我的第一通電話。
And somebody else might have hung up on
其他人可能已經結束通話電話
you, but I wouldn't do that, because I
你，但我不會那麼做，因為我
know about this stuff.
瞭解這個東西。
My mom killed herself.
我媽媽自殺了。
Really?
真的嗎？
Yes.
是的。
How?
如何？
I'm not gonna give you tips.
我不會給你提示。
Look, don't you see that this all came
瞧，你沒看到這一切都來了嗎？
together so that I could stop you from
一起這樣我就可以阻止你
doing this?
做這個？
Couldn't it just be a coincidence?
難道這只是巧合嗎？
No, it's fate.
不，這是命運。
That doesn't really seem like enough to be
這似乎還不夠
fate.
命運。
Oh, well, um, okay, here's a weird thing.
哦，好吧，好吧，這是一件奇怪的事情。
My mother was also a supply manager.
我的母親也是一名供應經理。
I'm actually the office manager.
我其實是辦公室經理。
Oh, my God, so was she!
天哪，她也是！
And get this, okay?
得到這個，好嗎？
Your name is Earl, right?
你叫厄爾，對吧？
Her name was Pearl.
她的名字叫珍珠。
P-Earl.
珍珠。
Was there anything else?
還有別的事嗎？
Sure.
當然。
Um, where are you from?
嗯，你來自哪裡？
Philadelphia.
費城。
Oh, my God, so was she!
天哪，她也是！
Oh, I've got, I've got goose, I've got
哦，我有，我有鵝，我有
goosebumps.
起雞皮疙瘩。
Really?
真的嗎？
Well, you know, I'm wearing layers and it's
嗯，你知道，我穿的是多層衣服
warm.
溫暖的。
Yeah, yeah.
是啊是啊。
But if you look, okay, these jerks might
但如果你看一下，好吧，這些混蛋可能
not care about you, but the universe does,
不在乎你，但宇宙在乎，
and that says a lot.
這說明瞭很多。
Did you hear that?
你聽到了嗎？
I don't need you guys to care about
我不需要你們關心
me because the universe cares!
我因為宇宙在乎！
The whole universe!
整個宇宙！
I really wish they'd care just a little
我真的希望他們能關心一點
bit more.
多一點。
You know, I don't think it's you.
你知道，我不認為是你。
This is a freaky place.
這是一個奇怪的地方。
Hey, guys!
嘿，夥計們！
Oh, no, it's you.
哦，不，是你。
Yeah.
是的。
Oh, this is terrible.
哦，這太可怕了。
Everything is destroyed.
一切都被摧毀了。
Look at this.
看看這個。
It obviously meant enough for me to save
這顯然對我來說已經足夠節省了
it, and I don't even know what it
它，我什至不知道它是什麼
is.
是。
It's still soft.
它還是軟的。
What do you think this is?
你覺得這是什麼？
Well, I think it was a mouse.
嗯，我認為那是一隻老鼠。
Aah!
啊啊！
Oh, my God!
我的天啊！
How are you, honey?
你好嗎，親愛的？
How do you think I am?
你覺得我怎麼樣？
You've wrecked all my childhood memories.
你毀了我所有的童年記憶。
You love Ross more than me, and I
你愛羅斯勝過愛我，而我
just rubbed a dead mouse on my face.
剛剛在我臉上擦了一隻死老鼠。
Sweetheart, we love you just as much as
親愛的，我們就像愛你一樣愛你
Ross.
羅斯.
Now, I'm sorry about everything that happened, and
現在，我對發生的一切感到抱歉，並且
I'll probably never be able to make it
我可能永遠無法做到
up to you, but here's a start.
由你決定，但這是一個開始。
What's this?
這是什麼？
It's the key to my Porsche.
這是我保時捷的鑰匙。
Well, the key to your Porsche.
嗯，這是你保時捷的鑰匙。
What?
什麼？
What?!
什麼？！
I've been thinking of getting rid of it,
我一直在想擺脫它
and I was driving it the other day,
那天我開著它，
and I saw my reflection in a store
我在一家商店裡看到了自己的倒影
window.
窗戶。
Your mother's right.
你媽媽是對的。
I do look like an ass.
我確實看起來像個屁股。
You're giving me your Porsche?
你把你的保時捷給我了？
You're kidding me, right?
你在開玩笑吧？
Well, wait a minute.
好吧，等一下。
I mean, a couple of stupid boxes get
我的意思是，有幾個愚蠢的盒子
wet, and she gets a Porsche?
濕透了，她卻得到了一輛保時捷？
Why don't we take it for a spin?
我們為什麼不試試看呢？
All right.
好的。
Well, what about me?
那麼，我呢？
I'm a medical marvel!
我是醫學奇蹟！
Oh, yeah.
哦，是的。
Uh...
呃...
Eh?
呃？
Uh-uh.
呃呃。
Hey, guys.
嘿，夥計們。
Hey.
嘿。
Do you know what happened to Chandler's Barca
你知道錢德勒的巴薩發生了什麼事嗎
lounger?
躺椅？
Oh, yeah, Joey broke it and had to
哦，是的，喬伊打破了它，不得不
get rid of it.
擺脫它。
Are you kidding?
你在開玩笑吧？
I get a Porsche and the Barca lounger's
我有一輛保時捷和巴薩躺椅
gone?
走了嗎？
This is the best day ever!
這是有史以來最好的一天！